TRISNA NADI SELAMET

Back End Development | Back End Engineer

Location: Bogor, Indonesia | No. Hp: +62812-9438-8977 | Email: nadi.selamet@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://trisna-nadi-selamet.github.io/Portfolio/

SUMMARY

I am a passionate person who enjoys creativity, and an IT programmer with knowledge of java programming languages. Experienced development two year with a demonstrated history of working in the manufacture and insurance industry. Strong professional with a bachelor's degree focused in technical informatic from universitas mercu buana.

EXPERIENCE

PT. Asuransi Jiwa Sinarmas MSIG – Jakarta, Indonesia

Financial Application Executive [Back End Development - Oct 2022 - Until now]

- Analyst mandays requirements project with businisse analyst.
- Creation design ERD structures model database.
- Make program code for applications to make it more secure.
- Overcome any problems that arise on the server side.
- Version control systems GITlab knowledge and experience.
- Deployment code for applications to server windows or linux.
- Methology Agile Scrum.
- The programming language java framework spring boot.

PT. Inspiro – Jakarta, Indonesia

Software Development [System Analyst – Mar 2022 – Oct 2022]

- Analyst mandays requirements project with development.
- Creation design ERD structures model database.
- Design use case, user story, scenario test and mockup application with figma.
- Methology Agile Scrum.
- The programming language java framework spring boot.

PT. Sinar Mas Multiartha, Tbk – Jakarta, Indonesia

Software Engineer [Back End Development – Aug 2021 – Mar 2022]

- Development of back end systems business unit.
- Creation of data structures model database.
- Design function cleaning data and validation Rest API.
- Version control systems GIT or SVN knowledge and experience.
- Methology SDLC.
- The programming language java framework spring boot.

EDUCATION

MERCU BUANA UNIVERSITY (2016 - 2020)

Bachelor's degree 2016 - 2020 Informatics IPK 3.37

CERTIFICATION

Certification Full-Stack Development.

Certification Algorithm Basic.

• Certification Database Basic.

• Certification Javascript.

Certification Java

TRAINING FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT

January 2021 – July 2021

Javascript

Github

Node Js

postgreSQL

React Js

LANGUAGE

Indonesia : Active English : Passive

OPERATING SYSTEM

- Windows
- Linux

SKILLS

- Jenkins
- Javascript
- Java
- Kubernetes

- OracleSQL
- PostgreSQL
- Hbase

SOFT SKILLS

- Time management
- Communication
- Detail Oriented
- Problem Solving